Hey everyone and thanks for jumping back
into the cryptoverse.
Today we're going to talk about Bitcoin
as it is now above $80,000. We are also
on the eve of Kevin Worsh speaking at
Jackson Hole tomorrow, which would be
Friday. So, we're going to talk about
that. If you guys like the content, make
sure you subscribe to the channel, give
the video a thumbs up, and again, check
out the sale on Into the Cryptoverse
Premium at into the cryptoverse.com.
As a reminder, the ticket prices for the
first ITC conference, Investing Through
the Cycles Conference, are going up on
September 1st. So, if you would like to
get your ticket, make sure you go ahead
and do so. Now, Bitcoin is trading back
above $80,000, and we are on the eve of
a fairly important event.
Kevin Walsh is going to be speaking
tomorrow at Jackson Hole. Now, if you
guys were here for the 2022
midterm year, you might remember that it
was Kevin or it was Jerome Powell coming
out on August in late August and saying
uh in very clear terms, there will be
pain and and the stock market reacted
negatively to that and it and it went
down into the low that we ended up
forming for that midterm year. Now Kevin
Walsh is a little bit different to say
the least when compared to Jerome
Powell. Kevin Walsh seems to be more of
the belief that forward guidance is not
really needed and he also recently said
that they expect essentially the long
end of the yield curve to do the work
for them. One of the issues right now is
that Kevin Worsh is saying that the long
end of the yield curve will do the work,
but you have treasur Treasury Secretary
Bessant uh you know essentially
accelerating their bond buyback program
thus trying to bring the long end the
yield curve down. So the problem is how
can they both work simultaneously? How
can how can Wor say just let the long
end do the work so that we don't have to
raise rates while you have the secretary
the Treasury secretary saying you know
what we're going to do basically what we
can to keep the long end down. So
there's an issue there because it it it
doesn't really allow for either of them
to kind of rely on what they were
previously, you know, perhaps relying on
and especially in terms of uh Kevin
Worsh, right? And and so what I think is
going to happen tomorrow is he's going
to get pressed on that. In fact, Stanley
Drunken Miller came out recently and and
wrote sort of a a fair a large criticism
of the bond buyback program that was
recently discussed by the Treasury
Secretary. And so then the question now
has become if that is brought up, how
will he respond to it? Now, that's a
lot, right? I mean, there's there's a
lot going on. As of right now, the odds
of a rate hike in September are somewhat
low according to the market, right?
There's only a one-third chance you're
going to get a rate hike in September. I
imagine the probabilities on this will
probably change some after the the
meeting in Jackson Hole and of course
after we get the next unemployment rate
uh labor market report that'll be coming
out next week. And so going into the to
the actual meeting, we should have a
better idea as to what's actually going
to happen.
So, where is Bitcoin now? Well, right
now, Bitcoin is at 80K. And I I've had a
lot of people ask, you know, is the
bottom end, right? Everyone wants to
know, is the bottom end? And to some
degree, remember, four-year cycle lows
don't always have to occur at the end of
the midterm year. There are examples in
the stock market where it occurs in the
summer, and we covered that previously.
be that as it may, just because it
sometimes occurs in the summer does not
unilaterally mean that Bitcoin's Bitcoin
cannot go back down. And so what I want
to talk about a little bit here is still
make the comparison to 2018, show you
guys certain fractalss and why fractals
are hard to put a lot of faith in
because they all look very similar, but
the eventual path can can be very very
different. So the first thing I want to
do here is look at 2018 and we can start
to see some divergence in it and maybe
and but we've also talked about how it's
not just 2018 but it's kind of like a
little 2019esque as well. In 2018
Bitcoin formed a low at around $6,000
and in 2026 that low was around $60,000.
Now what's interesting is the timing of
things have more or less lined up.
There's maybe some slight deviation.
Now, so in February of 2018, Bitcoin
formed a low at around $6,000. In
February of 2026, Bitcoin formed a low
at around $60,000. And then in late
March, early April, Bitcoin formed a
higher low in 2018 in the same way it
did so in 2026.
And then from there, Bitcoin formed a
lower high in May of both 2018
and 2026.
Obviously, I've been pretty bearish on
Bitcoin since last October, November
time frame, especially when Bitcoin fell
below the 50week moving average in
November. And um but that was sort of
like the final nail in the coffin to the
bare market. That was not the first
indicator of the bare market. That was
the last indicator that the bare market
was in fact here back in November of
2025. You can see that Bitcoin fell
below the 50we moving average right
there kind of early November time frame
and Bitcoin was still at around $100,000
or so a little over $100,000.
So what's interesting is that we've had
rallies
like we had in 2018, right? We had those
rallies and there every time we had a
rally there was all this emotion
associated with it. Tons of emotion.
Frankly, a lot of hate, right? A lot of
hate towards me for suggesting that the
bare market could come in 2026. But then
we fast forward and and it it did all
play out, right? Like the the rally in
in March and April last or earlier this
year, we look back on it and we're like,
"Yeah, counter trend rally." We look
back on the rally that we had back in
in, you know, December and early January
and we can say, yep, it was a counter
trend rally. There was no reason there
was no reason for the emotions to get to
the point that they did. But that did
not stop the emotions from getting to
that point anyways, right? Because, and
I've said this before, whenever the
market's going up, it feels like it will
never go down again. Whenever the
market's going down, it feels like it
will never go up again. So let's just go
through again where has it been similar
and is it starting to deviate because we
want to be a student of the market. We
want to say has this happened before? Is
there any precedent for it or would it
make more sense to just get on the bull
bandwagon and and not even consider
further downside? Well, as I will remind
you, and I know people don't like
listening to this part because there's a
difference between being right and
making money, as I've said countless
times, and on July 1st, I was very
clear. I said it on YouTube, I said it
on Twitter, that the accumulation window
for Bitcoin, in my opinion, had begun,
right? But that with that, we could go
lower in the fourth quarter of the year.
And the reason for that is because I was
looking back at how I had played the
last two cycles and saying, you know
what, the last two cycles I started
buying Bitcoin in the second half of the
midterm year. In both cases, there was a
rally that made me believe the bottom
was in in some cases. Last like I wasn't
really believing the bottom was in, you
know, and then it came later. But in
2018, I thought the bottom was in uh by
the summer and then we ended up going
lower later on. And so sort of the thing
to think about here is
have we seen this type of move before
that then
led to price coming back down. I don't
have a crystal ball unfortunately. I
cannot sit here and tell you with 100%
confidence what is going to happen. I
can say that there is a slight deviation
in the 2018 move and we'll talk about
that now. So, if you look at the how
it's formed so far, you have a February
low in 2018 and 2026. You have a higher
low in late March, early April of both
years. You have a lower low in the
summer where you swept where you go
below either 6,000 for 2018 or 60,000
for 2026. And then, of course, you have
your lower high in May. All of that
played out in the exact same way. It all
played out. Now, what happened after
Bitcoin swept the low in the summer of
2018? Well, after Bitcoin swept the low,
it rallied back up to the 50week moving
average, right? That's what happened. It
rallied to the 50week moving average.
This is a statement. I am not making a
projection on that. It's just this is
what happened. We swept the low. Bitcoin
rallied to the 50we. Now, when Bitcoin
swept the low in July, I said then
that Bitcoin
could go back up to the 50WE moving
average in the same way that it did in
2018. But this is where it deviates and
this is where it it surprised me a
little bit if I'm being honest. And as
I've said before, we're all going to
make mistakes. We're not going to be
right about absolutely everything. I'd
be lucky to be right about 55% of things
if we're being honest. But this is kind
of where it deviates a little. All
right, so after we swept the low in the
summer, I said, "All right, that will
likely be the low for a while." And the
reason for that is because the low ended
up being 57,000.
The reason why 57,000 is important is
because the low in 2018 also happened to
be 5700.
Right? And again, I I know this is silly
and and people get annoyed by some of
this type of analysis, but you cannot
deny that in 2026 it has mimicked a lot
of 2018 as the cycle has gone on. If you
look at say the year-to- date ROI of
Bitcoin, I'm not really I just had it
up. I didn't realize that was up. So,
let me bring it back up. If you look at
the year-to- date ROI of Bitcoin in 2026
and compare it to 2018, you will see a
lot of similarities, right? Lows form
around the same time. The lower highs
form around the same time. The main
difference is the rally to the 50we has
not occurred at the same time. In 2018,
the rally to the 50we occurred by late
July. Now, it's occurring in August.
So what happened back then was we
immediately, you can see we swept the
low at 50. We went to 5700. We went up,
consolidated for one week down, and then
we went straight up to the 50we moving
average as you can see, right? Straight
up to that 50week moving average and
then we sold off. The reason why this
time is different and it it it's not
necessarily the same exactly is because
this time after sweeping the low at
57,000 we consolidated for far longer
than we did in 2018. Remember 2018 was
like two green weeks up, one red one red
week down and then up to the 50 week.
This one was four green weeks up and
then two red weeks down with a green
week in between. And so it took
basically an extra month before the
rally to the 50we even occurred. But if
you're not married to the timing of it,
it it played out in the same way. It's
just that it's played out later this
time. Now, the reason why this is so
hard is because you would expect a rally
from a low to look the same way. And and
let me show you what I mean, right? If
you were to take say a bar pattern from
the last cycle low, right, from the last
low, the last cycle and and just simply
overlay this on the chart, this is what
you would expect it to look like, right?
And you can that's that's the uh 2022
move. You can also take the, you know,
the um uh some of the other moves,
right? You could look at at 2019 and and
look at how 2019 is. You can see that
again ignoring the pandemic. This is
sort of how it played out. Like you had
a rally, right? You had a rally that
occurred. You you sort of sold off, you
had a rally up, you came back down, you
had another rally up, then the pandemic
hit, and then you sold off. You have
2018, right? If we take the the 2018
move, it's very similar. It's just it it
occurred a month later. So for me,
what's difficult here is is which one do
you put faith in, right? Because again,
they all sort of line up, right? Where
you have the fractal where it drops
down, it rallies up, it drops down
again, it rallies to the 50we, and then
it sells off again, and then eventually
it it resolves to downside. So because
of that I I cannot take a fractal and
say that it has to play out this way
because if I look at the 2022 fractal
it would look like there's a good
there's a case to be made that the low
is in right when you when you sort of
line that up. So this is what makes it
hard. A rally off the low a true low
would look the same that it looks right
now. If it looked different from what it
looks like right now, it'd be a lot
harder to believe that it's the low
because normally when the low is formed,
you just go straight up. Now, in 2018,
we rallied to the 50we and got rejected.
In 2023, we rallied to the 50we and
broke through.
In 2015, we rallied to the 50we and got
rejected.
the cycle before we rallied to the 50we
temporary rejection but ultimately we
broke through. So the question now is do
we break through or do we not? And I I I
think that we're about to have the
answer to that question and that doesn't
mean we can't have a fake out first in
either direction. So, we're going to
zoom in now to 2018 and look and I want
you to look closely at how it played out
in 2018 and that way we can assess if
it's evolving differently
or the same. All right?
Don't get married to a thesis. Just just
look to see if it's going to play out
the same way or if it's different. in
2018. If 2018, if you look at the low
that was formed in February and you
basically just connect the dots, what
you'll see, you you take your February
low to your March high, your March
higher low, and then you can see where
you broke down. And then it was when we
broke down, that's what formed the
summer low that we talked about. That
would likely be the low for a little
bit. That's what formed the summer low.
But after the summer low was formed,
Bitcoin rallied up to that trend line,
right? Like it it basically was going
back up and and retesting the trend line
that it broke down from. It tested it
temporary rejection. You see that long
wick up on a red day? Keep that in mind.
Long red, long red wick up. We then came
back up to the trend line and then the
next day there was a big move above it
probably faking everyone out
and then a couple weeks later we gave it
all back.
Back then Bitcoin rallied from 5700
up to 8,400.
Back then 8,400 roughly was the 50week
moving average. I think it was maybe
slightly lower. I believe we wicked
above the 50week moving average back
then, but you can see it went up to
about 848,500
and then a week or two later, we were
basically just giving it all back. So
remember that pattern though, the higher
sort of the higher lows into the summer
into the summer low and then a rally
back up to the trend line consolidation
and then blast through only for it to be
given back.
Okay,
what's interesting,
you can already picture it, right? You
already know what I'm going to say
because it's the same thing, right? I
mean, it's the exact same thing. It's
just the month that it's occurring is a
month later. You take your higher lows,
right? You take your February low to
your your March higher low. Remember
that red wick up, that wick back up. See
that red wick to the to the trend line?
That also occurred in in 2018 as well,
right? You can see it. And I'll zoom
back in.
See that wick red day wick up to the
trend line, get rejected for a couple
days, and then right back up to it.
That's where we are right now, right?
like we're we're right back up to it to
the to where the wick was. So, if you go
back to 2026,
there's the red wick back down going
right back up to that level, which
coincidentally
or maybe not coincidentally happens to
be the 50week moving average. Now,
Jackson Hole is tomorrow. Kevin Wars is
speaking.
In 2018, Bitcoin wicked above the 50week
moving average on the day that it broke
through the trend line. Right? Like it
broke through the trend line, wicked
above the 50we moving average, and then
the next week it sold off
in 2023 when we got above it, we sort of
sold off, but then eventually we we
broke through.
This is why it's so hard is because if
you are a believer in the 2018 analog,
it's not like this is that different
from what we've previously seen. Now,
where it is different is the fact that
the high that it's making, wherever it
makes, is actually near the prior high
in May. In 2018, the high at the 50we
was a lot lower than the one in May,
right? I mean, significantly lower
because the one in May was at like
10,000 basically the in 2018. In 2026,
the one in May was not at 100K, right?
It was only at like 82,000. But this is
where it's not just the 2018 analog if
the bare market is to play out that we
have to consider. There's other analoges
as well. You could look at 2019 where we
rallied back up to a high. That's not
the best example because the pandemic
occurred. But I would like to know what
would have happened had the pandemic not
occurred. Would it would we have broken
through or like would we have just sold
off in a slower fashion, gone to the
same levels and then gone up?
Maybe timebased capitulation would have
still played out. But because price
based capitulation occurred,
it accelerated it. Okay, now you might
say, "Well, Ben, we only got one example
where we went back up to a high only to
get rejected and then back up." There's
actually two more examples in 2014,
right? 2014 is a great example where we
formed a low, right? Okay, we formed a
low in February. We rallied up, we came
back down, swept the low,
and then right back up. Right? You see
that high? So you you you set a low in
February, rally up, set a lower low,
rally up to the same level
only to get rejected and go down. And
when it got rejected and went down, it
actually formed a low. The next low
occurred coincidentally in October. This
also occurred in 2015 as well. In 2015,
we set a low, rallied up, set a higher
low, rallied back up to the 50we, got
rejected, went down, formed the actual
low in a recession scare. Not a
recession. There was a recession scare
and then we went up.
I'll be honest with you guys, okay?
What happens with Bitcoin from here, in
my opinion, doesn't really matter what
Kevin Walsh says tomorrow. None of that
to me is is is going to really make or
break anything. I mean, if he if he
comes out really doubbish, maybe Bitcoin
breaks through. Uh what I think a lot of
this comes down to is whether we get a
correction in the stock market or not.
That's what it comes down to. because
every prior low in the market for
Bitcoin occurred near the end of the
midterm year in 2014. It actually
occurred in early really early 2015, but
basically the end of the midterm year.
And every single one of those
corrections corresponded to a stock
market correction that started in either
August or September. Right? In every
single case, you had a a drop in stocks
that occurred. Right? Here it is. Not it
was in 2014. it was just a 10% drop.
2018 it was a 20% drop. 2022 it was a 20
20% drop. Right? Every single midterm
year for stocks for the last three
midterm years had that 10 to 20% drop in
the index right in the stock market and
then Bitcoin during that event went back
down in Q4 and then that's where the
actual low occurred.
The way in which I could be wrong about
that view would be if there's not a
stock market correction. If instead of
the stock market getting a correction
like it normally does starting in either
August or mid to late September,
if it doesn't happen, then there is
always a chance that the low is in at
57K. That doesn't mean we won't
eventually go below it. um if things
evolve in a in a bad way later on but
that's the window right like that that
window of weakness would be then if it's
going to happen in my opinion and that's
why I say you know what happens here at
the 50we is crucial because if the low
is in like it was in 2022 you would
expect to break through the 50we moving
average if the low is in like it was in
by early 2019, then we should break
through the 50week moving average on
multiple weekly closes.
If this is more like a fake out, then
you would expect Bitcoin to get rejected
between 80 to 85K because in 2018 we
went up to almost 8,500, right? You
would that is where the rejection would
theoretically occur at. So for me, it
would not make a lot of sense to stay
bearish if Bitcoin starts accepting on
multiple weekly closes in the in the
mid80s, right? Like at that point, it
really calls into question the validity
of the continuation of the bare market.
If that does not happen, if Bitcoin just
simply is stalls out between 80 and 85,
you could argue that we've seen this
before. Now, the reason why a lot of
people believe the low is in, and they
could be right. Like, I'm not here to
say that they're wrong. I mean, I we
don't know, but one of the reasons is
because it looks very similar to the
2022 low. And there are some indicators
that would suggest that could be the
low. If you were to look at the Bitcoin
supply in profit or loss,
I mean, it looks like, you know, a
fairly aesthetically pleasing chart. I
made a video on this on July 1st, I
believe, called, you know, uh, an
aesthetically pleasing chart or
something like that or a beautiful chart
and you can see just how clear this
stuff is. But sometimes you get these
big drops in it like we did in 2015 and
then it just sells off again. So again,
just because it came down here doesn't
mean it can't cross again. But the point
is is if you're only looking at this
chart, you wouldn't look at this chart
and be bearish. You would look at the
chart and be like, "Well, look, we
reset. It's time to be build. It's time
to be bullish.
If you were to look at the RSI, say the
weekly RSI, you could say, "Look, we
reset. Why do we need to go lower?
Why, you know, do we need to?" No, we
don't need to. But you can look at the
weekly RSI and say, "Look, every single
cycle we go down below 30 and then that
ends up being the bottom around those
levels."
So, that's a case to be made.
You can see that we're kind of coming up
to these lower highs in the weekly RSI.
But the counterpoint
to this is there are indicators that do
not suggest that. For instance, looking
at the realized price, and I'm going to
probably put a video soon called the
bulls versus the bears, and we'll go
through everything, at least everything
I can think of. The realized price, the
realized price in 2014 was not crossed
until October.
The realized price in 2018 was not
crossed until November.
In 2022, we crossed the realized price
in June. This cycle, we haven't crossed
it. So again, it makes it made sense to
say that we would form a low in the
summer because there are some indicators
that suggest the low is in, but not all
indicators suggest the low is in. So
what I would argue is that if the low is
not in, which we should find out in the
next two weeks or so, if we either get
rejected or we break through the 50we,
if the low is not in, then the next
major area to look at for support would
in fact be the realized price, right?
Like 53 $53,000. That's where the
realized price is. It would be just
going slightly below the prior level,
right? Like not even that far below it.
maybe even just kind of connecting the
dots on some of this stuff, just saying,
"All right, we go down a little bit
lower, we hit 53K, and then that is the
low, but even then, you still would not
have all onchain indicators reset." So,
I don't want to get ahead of myself, you
know, I I don't want to get out into
that type of analysis at the current
time when everyone's just screaming for
new alltime highs at this point. And I
know there's a lot of people that truly
from the bottom of their heart
absolutely despise me right now for
suggesting that we could in fact have a
lower low and then now they feel like
they're left behind in the market. But I
will reiterate
as I said the second half of the midterm
year in my opinion is the time to
accumulate right? Like I'm not telling
you to time the bottom. I'm saying look
what I do is I buy Bitcoin in the second
half of midterm years and I just deal
with the rallies right I mean you know I
I deal with the rallies and if I'm not
fully allocated I'm not but in 2018
after I started buying Bitcoin had a
almost a 50% rally in 2022 after I
started buying Bitcoin had about a 40%
rally right I mean I started buying in
July like I said and and again we're up
about 40%.
It's not like we haven't seen it before.
The question is is which indicators do
you want to put your faith in? Do you
want to put your faith in the RSI and
the supply and profit and loss and and
that sort of stuff and the fractal of
2022 or do you want to put your faith in
in the more cautious indicators like the
realized price or the balance price and
that sort of stuff? It's all a matter of
what do you want to put your faith in in
terms of calling the low or not.
So,
tomorrow is a big day. We got Kevin
Walsh speaking at Jackson Hole. We'll
see if it continues to follow 2018 or
not. I think we'll have an answer to all
this stuff within the next week or two
because the reality is
if if this is a true breakout
beyond a shadow of a doubt, right? If
this is a true breakout,
Bitcoin should get above the 50 without
much issue. It might stall out a little
bit, right? And maybe it'll wick above
it a couple, but it should get above it
without issue like it did in 2023 and
like it did in 2019.
But we can't know that yet, right? Like
there there's plenty of historical
examples
like 2015
and like 2018 where we simply just got
rejected by it. And I you know in 2015
the rally that we had off the low
was also about 40%. Right? And we still
got rejected went down to a lower low.
It's a tough market right? It's a tough
market. Please remember there is a
difference between being right and
making money. You don't have to be right
about everything to make money in the
market, right? I mean, this midterm year
I was more bullish on stocks and I was
buying index funds and energy and
manufacturing stocks. Those did really
well. Bitcoin has struggled against all
of them. Even with the current rally,
you can make money even in bare markets
as long as you know where the bull
market is. And right now we're basically
in the in the moment of figuring out if
the bare market is simply going to
continue or not. And you can take a
side.
I admittedly am probably one of the more
risk averse crypto YouTubers, right?
Probably one of the more risk averse. So
I am always going to look for the risk.
I'm not ever going to sit here and tell
you there's no risk, right? I won't ever
do that. So, if you want to get mad
about that,
comment sections down below. But that's
just who I am. That's who I've always
been. Well, maybe not who I always been,
but it's been who who I've been for the
last say seven or eight years. That's
who I am. That's who I will be in the
future. And I will continue to talk
about this stuff in as objective of a
way as I can.
And if we break through on weekly clo on
on two or three weekly closes cuz we
sometimes we'll get like one or two but
if there's no followthrough if we break
through I will come here and say all
right I'm dropping the bare thesis. I
will say that and I I will not hold on
to it. I will say it clear and simple. I
have no problem admitting when I am
wrong. And if I'm wrong I'm wrong.
But again, I guarantee you the people
that trolled me at these other highs,
none of them came out for the most part.
None of them came out and and said
anything other than just started to bull
post the same way. So, but I will I will
I will come out and say I'm wrong. If we
accept above the the the low to mid50 or
the low to mid 80s, accepting above
that, especially like 85k,
the bare case is tough, right? The bare
case is really really tough at that
point. and and then it just wouldn't
make sense. Um, but those are my views.
I hope it's helpful. Uh, again, I don't
I don't have a crystal ball. Some of you
guys might have one. So, if you do, I'
I'd ask you to assess what your crystal
ball is telling you. And finally, the
last thing is that if you
truly do believe the low is in beyond a
shadow of a doubt, right? Let's say you
believe this is like a 2018 style move
without the final breakdown. Okay?
Don't let a 30% rally off the low scare
you, right? I mean, like, it would be
like not buying Bitcoin in 2023 because
it was at 20K instead of 15 or not
buying it in 2019 because it was at
5,000 instead of 3,000
at some point. I know it feels like
you're chasing, but if you truly are
like if you're truly mad and you're
like, "Oh, you know, I thought the low
was in Q4 and now you're determined.
You're you know the low already
occurred."
Okay, so what? Right? Maybe you picked
up a little bit there, you add here, and
then in a year or two, you're not going
to care anyways. So, don't, you know,
don't don't let missing the beginning of
a move force you to miss the entire
thing. Okay? If you missed the 2019 move
here, you didn't have to sit out for the
next two years watching the market go
up. Same thing in 2023. If you missed
the first move, you don't have to sit
out for two years watching the market go
up. Same thing here. So if at any point
you're convinced the low is in and you
feel this like righteous anger that you
missed out and now you have to sit on
the sidelines for the next two years,
you don't, right? Like you don't. You
can always get a position and you live
with the consequences no matter what.
And you don't blame anyone else either.
It's your decision. It's your money. You
do with it what you please. If you buy
and we go up, it's your it's what you
do, right? And if you if you don't buy
and we go down, don't thank me. Don't
thank me because I already started
buying Bitcoin in July when we went
below.3 risk. My my own my own issue
that I have is that I told you guys for
the entire first half of midterm year
that I would start buying in July
below.3 risk. And we went there and I
had all the five days at those levels to
accumulate in the second half of the
midterm year below.3s. Only 5 days.
So I bought some. It's not like it's not
like my position isn't up.
It's not what I would want it to be,
right? Let's be honest, right? I mean,
like it's not like I'm fully allocated,
but it's also not like I have nothing
either. I'm trying to communicate my
strategy with you guys. Uh hopefully
that's been helpful. If it hasn't, you
know, there's other people you guys can
follow. Thank you guys for tuning in.
Make sure you subscribe. Uh give the
video a thumbs up. And again, if you
guys want to come to the conference in
November, uh you know, late November,
we'll see what the market's doing by
then. Uh make sure you guys get your
ticket before September 1st as prices
are going up. Then thank you guys for
tuning in and I'll see you next time.
Bye.